mp3rocketsearch.com 2016-02-10

# mp3rocket.toolbaroptions.com - Privacy Policy

Powered by Jookz Toolbar Platform.

1\. **No spyware:** Jookz does not collect identifiable information from toolbar users and does not monitor personal toolbar usage.

## Jookz collects the following information:

  * From toolbar users: Jookz does not collect (and the toolbar does not transmit) information that can personally identify a toolbar user and does not track URLs visited by toolbar users.

The toolbar sends unidentifiable, non-personal statistical data to Jookz's servers to help us improve our services and our product support. This non-personal data includes a count of clicks on toolbar components and unidentifiable toolbar queries. Toolbar users can opt not to send such statistical data at any time from their Toolbar Options dialog box.

Jookz may share with a toolbar Publisher aggregated and non-personal data about clicks on toolbar components by its toolbar users. Such data is solely used to help the Publisher improve and enrich his community toolbar.

Jookz does not otherwise share personal information about a Publisher or a toolbar user with any third party, unless doing so is necessary to carry out a request by the Publisher or the user or required to protect the legal rights of Jookz or any third party.

Jookz does not collect personal information that toolbar users may voluntarily submit while using toolbar components. Such information may be kept on the user's local computer (such as information used by the Email Notifier component) or by third parties that the toolbar user may opt to communicate with directly.

2\. **No adware:** Jookz does not place advertisements on toolbar components and does not require toolbar users to be exposed to ads. The toolbar does not launch pop-up or pop-under advertisement windows or any other type of obtrusive ads.

3\. **Unobtrusive:** The toolbar does not enable applications to access data stored by toolbar users on their hard drive or in online accounts without their permission. The toolbar does not modify pages visited by toolbar users and does not hijack searches.

4\. **Easy uninstall:** Toolbar users can easily uninstall their toolbar at any time using our standard uninstall package (Add/Remove Programs in Windows, Add-on Removal in Firefox, etc.).

5\. **Easy deactivation:** Toolbar users can deactivate their toolbar at any time by clicking the View menu in their browser and deselecting the name of their community toolbar.

6\. **Full control:** Toolbar users can add/remove toolbar components at any time using their Toolbar Options dialog box.

7\. **"Tell-A-Friend":** Toolbar users may opt to invite a friend to use a certain community toolbar via the "Tell-A-Friend" link offered by Jookz and available in their toolbar. Jookz will not use the information submitted by the user for any purpose other than sending a one-time invitation to the friend as per the user's request.

8\. **Publisher compliance:** All Publishers of community toolbars powered by Jookz must fully comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Publishers must disclose a similar privacy policy to all of their toolbar users using a direct and permanent link in their toolbar. In the event that the Publisher chooses to implement a privacy policy of his own, the Publisher must make his policy available from his toolbar, notify his users about the policy and ensure that the policy is at least as protective of toolbar users' privacy rights as this Jookz Community Toolbar Privacy Policy. Publishers must notify their toolbar users about changes they apply to toolbar components that may affect the users' privacy rights. It is the Publisher's responsibility to obtain an approval from toolbar users in such cases, as may be applicable.

9\. **Safety:** As a platform provider, Jookz allocates significant resources to maintaining a clean and secure platform. However, we cannot be responsible for third-party content added to our platform via our APIs or our customization and personalization features. For your safety and security, it is important to download and install software only from publishers you trust, whether toolbars or any other software.

10\. **Updates:** In the event that we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on our website and revise the "last updated" date on the document. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we protect the privacy rights of our Publishers and their users. A continued use of our platform and products constitutes an agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

11\. **Contact us:** If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to report to us about violations of this policy or other privacy-related issues, please do not hesitate to contact us via email at [toolbaroptions.privacy@toolbaroptions.com](mailto:toolbaroptions.privacy@toolbaroptions.com?subject=Toolbar%20Questions).
